Hello everyone, welcome back to another edition of This Just In.
I am joined in the studio, as always, with Leonardo Guerrero.
Hello!
And also from Spanish part today, a special guest, Liliana Mata.
Hola!
She's back!
I'm back for more.
I never thought she was going to be back.
Yeah, it's Liliana Reloaded.
Of course, yeah.
She never gives up.
Yeah, she never gives up.
This is vengeance.
And, well, we're going to be looking at the normal stuff, as always, but we have
really exciting news.
What are the news?
What are you talking about?
Well, do you want the news first, or the lessons first?
Ah, news.
Yeah, is it good news or bad news?
It's bad news.
Good news.
You sure?
Alright, so the first news that we have, so we're coming out with the user survey
and you're going to be able to give us some feedback.
We need to know who you are, where you are, and what you want.
How is that good news for me?
It's good news because the first 100 users who respond will receive one free month's
worth of English power.
Whoa!
I know.
So all you have to do is just take, it literally takes 5 to 10 minutes of your time,
fill out this survey, and if you're among the first 100 people, you get a free month.
Oh, so you are that one.
I got a notice from the marketing manager today, and he told me, hey, dude, we're
going to need to give 100, one month premium free to English pod users.
I'm like, what?
Yeah, 100.
So how are we going to do that?
Well, it's your problem.
So I'm going to have to do it manually for you.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm sorry.
But that's your job.
See, that's why you get the big bucks.
That's true.
Yeah.
The marketing manager doesn't call you dude.
Yeah, he does.
Sometimes.
It's Ross.
Oh, true.
It's more like, hey, dude.
Yeah, that's true.
It's Grant.
Is it Grant?
All right.
So a big shout out to our marketing manager who made this possible.
Yeah.
Thank you, marketing manager.
All right.
So be sure to follow the link on the website and then you can go to the survey.
It's an online survey, so you don't have to send anything through mail or print
anything.
Wow.
All right.
Second good news.
Now English pod has a new feature.
We have daily update emails.
Yeah, that's cool.
You can click and notify and follow up all these emails.
Right.
We have an option where on the email, you're going to get one email every day,
which is going to tell you the activity that's been going on on the website.
So kind of like in Jammer.
Something like Yammer.
Like Facebook.
Kind of like Facebook.
Exactly.
Yes.
It's when you comment or something and then someone else comments and they just
tell you, oh, someone come in on your picture, your comment and this.
Yeah.
But you know, like Facebook will send you like 20 emails, right?
We're going to send you one with a summary of everything that's happened.
That's even better.
Yeah.
I know.
Take that Facebook.
In your face Facebook.
All right.
So you can turn this option on and off by clicking on the box under comment.
Mm hmm.
Okay.
And you have to wait for the little green thing that it says updating.
Because if you click it and you don't see that green thing that it says updating,
that means it didn't save.
Okay.
It didn't work.
You have to just pay attention to that.
Right.
So yeah, don't leave the page or just be a little bit patient.
So two new things, good news with this new feature and the survey.
The survey is really important because we want to know who you are.
We want to know how we can serve you better.
So we need to know where you are, where our listeners are coming from, how old you are,
what you do for a living, et cetera.
Do we accept minors?
Yeah, of course.
We have some listeners who are like under 18, they're like 16 or 17 preparing for school
or something.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I watch my language.
The other thing is that our users are all over the place.
We have people from Russia.
We have people from, um, from Mexico, baby, Mexico.
We have a lot of listeners in the United States, in Brazil.
Do you have people from Kenya?
From Kenya?
No, we don't.
Do you have people from?
Yes, you have.
All right.
Is this, are these Spanish pod listeners that you have in Kenya and Qatar and Israel?
And we have so many people, some, okay, I'm not going to brag.
Really?
Wow.
Where are they from?
Well, the number one city that listens to Spanish pod is London.
London?
London, baby.
Wow.
Like our stuff.
Interesting.
Uh, we have a lot of listeners in Russia and Brazil, specific cities.
I'm not really sure, but yeah, we are pretty global.
So we want to know where you are and we want to serve you better.
And now for next week's lessons, all right.
So on lessons next week, we're going to start with a small series of old English,
but not like really, really old, like Shakespeare old.
We're going to start with no, like 1950s, like, Hey, yeah, you know, like swell and swell.
I heard that in, uh, this series is called Mad Men.
Mad Men.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's kind of like set in the fifties.
You were swell.
Yeah.
So we are going to have a series of English.
We're starting with the 1950s.
We're going to go into the 1960s, 70s, 80s, 90s, and modern day English slang that
were used back then, or they're still used now.
So that's going to be cool.
Do you think English, but we can use it low and high?
Yeah, of course you can.
Do you actually think we can be able to learn anything else like new?
New?
Yeah.
Why not?
I'm just asking.
Just tell me a word from these fifties that I wouldn't know.
Pipsqueak.
Exactly.
Wow.
I don't know that.
I don't know that either.
Pipsqueak?
Pipsqueak.
What is that?
Pipsqueak and Quik.
Yeah, because there was Pepsi back in the day.
There was in the fifties.
Oh, yeah.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Not in the fifties.
Yeah, there was.
Pepsi.
Yeah.
I don't know if Quik was there.
I don't know if Pepsi in the fifties.
Yeah, definitely.
Maybe it was called something else though.
I know it had another name.
It was Pepsi-Cola.
Wasn't it?
Well, yeah.
It's still kind of Pepsi-Cola.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
Anyways.
What does it mean?
Pipsqueak.
Pipsqueak is like this small, annoying person.
Like Leo?
Like Léo?
So you would say like, hey, Pipsqueak, kind of like.
You're such a Pipsqueak.
We are, Léo.
A Pipsqueak.
Thank you.
All right, so.
And now also we're going to have another lesson from our series, sports series.
We're going to be learning about volleyball.
Nice.
Game, point, match.
Volleyball.
Ram.
You said earlier.
You have kind of a volleyball beard.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that's because you have six hairs on one side and six on the other.
Like in volleyball.
By the way, I haven't shaved like for three weeks already.
And he still has three hairs.
They're just like longer.
But I'm not going to shave ever again.
No, please don't do that.
Ever.
Why did you choose this?
Why did you come upon this?
Because he's trying to annoy me.
Because I've been having a good strike with girls.
Oh, really?
With facial hair.
Yeah.
Really.
They don't complain when you kiss them that it itches or it feels weird.
No, it's actually fine, actually.
I actually asked them because I was like concerned.
I felt dirty.
Yeah, well, you look dirty, but I mean.
Not in a good way.
There's a good way of looking dirty.
It depends on the.
Yes.
It depends on the girl.
There are some girls that don't like it, but there are some that they do.
Some girls dig facial hair.
So yeah, there's been quite a few girls that say, oh, you look fine.
You look fine.
So I'll keep it.
No, no, no.
I think a beard or a mustache or a goatee.
That's OK.
But you have like seriously no form like do you see that space right in the middle of
his cheek?
There's hair there just by itself.
It's like an island of hair.
Do you see that?
Maybe we should.
OK, you know what?
Maybe we should like get a trimmer and just like give you some form.
Yes.
We can do like a Backstreet Boy type.
No, I won't shave ever again.
You know what?
I'm going to blow out a picture from this and you can you guys.
You can be the judge.
We can do a before and after picture.
Yes.
Let's do that.
And we'll let the users decide.
And if more users vote that you should shave, you're going to have to shave.
All right.
Let's do it.
Users, I believe in you.
I want to keep it.
All right.
So apart from Leo's volleyball beard and volleyball lesson that we're going to have
on Wednesday, on Friday, we're actually going to be talking about a topic that was covered
previously in Spanish Pod.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Well, let me tell you why he's laughing because a lot of his brilliant ideas come from Spanish
Pod.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
My lessons.
Oh, no.
Whoa.
No?
Tell me one lesson.
OK.
This lesson.
The Big Band.
That's the lesson that we have on Friday.
You see?
That's it.
OK.
Check, guys.
All right.
But the topic is the same, but the way that it's being treated is different.
Yeah.
You change two words.
No, no.
I got to be with Lian and this one.
Thank you.
Other than that, we've never taken any other dialogue from Spanish Pod.
Whatever.
You better not.
Come on.
Our dialogues are award-winning.
Well, of what?
Yeah.
Of quality, of sound effects, of engineering.
Tell me one word.
Spanish Pod has two words, actually.
Yeah.
English Pod.
We also won.
We won a Banff Audio Festival Award.
Banff?
Yeah.
You don't even know where Banff is.
It's in Canada.
Where in Canada?
Near Sunshine Village.
Say that.
Sunshine Village.
It's true.
Isn't it near Sunshine Village?
Isn't it or isn't it not?
It's not.
Yes, it is.
No, it's not.
It's in Banff.
Oh, no, no.
Nikiska's in Banff.
It's in Banff.
Okay.
Let's go to the next lesson.
Anyways.
It was the third lesson.
The Big Bang Theory.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
So the Big Bang Theory is an advanced lesson, right?
So we're going to be talking about these advanced notions of particles, antiparticles, dark
matter, and all these crazy concepts of the theory of how the world and the universe
are going to be different.
So let's go.
Okay.
And all these crazy concepts of the theory of how the world and the universe came to
be.
The Zack Vader comes from the dark matter?
No, he doesn't.
But he could.
We all come from dark matter.
Are you kidding me?
We're going to start talking about Star Wars?
No, we already had lessons on Star Wars.
Oh, really?
Do you already have one for Star Trek?
Yes, we did.
Ooh, Star Trek.
We already have one.
Did you guys see the new movie?
Not yet.
We saw it together, Leo.
Oh, yeah.
In IMAX.
It was amazing.
Yes.
And I'm not a Star Trek fan, huh?
Me either.
Don't take me wrong.
I never knew anything.
I'm not a geek.
Yeah, me neither.
I mean, with all the respect for the Star Trek fans.
No, it's not Star Trek fans.
They're called Trekkies.
Trekkies.
There you go.
You're one of those.
You're a Trekkie now.
I am.
I haven't seen it yet, but I hope that I will see it soon.
You should go.
I will.
All right, guys.
So that's it for today.
I hope you enjoyed it.
If you have any questions, any comments, please come to the website.
There's no user of the week because nobody deserved it.
Yeah.
We've actually going to maybe start picking user of the week every two weeks.
But again, we have to praise all of the users, you know, Cuevas and Maxim and Steve.
Also, you know, actually Steve from Spanish Pod.
He's on our site.
Stevester?
Yeah, Stevester.
Stevester.
What are you doing here?
Yeah, no.
Come back, Stevester.
He's one of our all-star.
He's like a famous guy on the site because he helps users and he corrects their grammar.
Oh, that's so nice of him.
This is true.
I hope he listens to this podcast, but Stevester actually helps me with my English.
Really?
Yeah, he's great.
With mine, too.
See?
So, Stevester, thank you very much.
You are amazing.
Thank you for helping not only our users, but also Liliana and Leo.
Yes.
Thank you.
All right.
And we'll see everyone else there.
Until next time.
Bye.
See ya.
Bye-bye.
EnglishPod.com.